-I'm sorry! -That is it!
-抱歉 -天啊,我受够了
You barge in here and you don't knock?
你不敲门就闯进来?
You have no respect for privacy. No,you wait!
-难道你不尊重别人的隐私权? -不,你慢着
-Can I just say one thing? -What?!
-我能说一件事吗? -什么事?
That's a relatively open weave. I can still see...
这块布编的非常松,我仍能看见…
...your nippular areas.
…你的胸脯
The One With The Boobies
六人行 第1季 第13集 看胸脯
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 荣誉出品 河马根据网络字幕微调制作
Honey,tell them the story about your patient...
亲爱的,告诉他们你的病人
...who thinks things are other things.
如何把事想成另一件事
When the phone rings and she takes a shower.
例如电话响时她就去洗澡
That's pretty much it.
差不多是那样
-But you tell it really well,sweetie. -Thanks. Okay.
-但你说得很好 -谢谢
Now go away so we can talk about you.
快走开我们才能谈你
Okay. I'll miss you.
好吧,我会想念你的
-lsn't he great? -He's cute. He likes you so much.
-他很不错吧 -他好帅,也好像很喜欢你
I know. He's so sweet. And so complicated,you know?
我知道,他人很好,而且很复杂
And for a shrink, he's not too shrinky.
有点神经质,但是有又不是太神经质
Think you'll do it on his couch?
他会在沙发上做吗?
I don't know. That's a little weird.
我不知道…有点奇怪
It's vinyl.
聚乙稀做的
Okay,you guys want anything else?
大家还想要别的吗?
-Could I have? -We're all out. Anybody else?
-要,我要… -抱歉,卖完了,其他人呢?
Did I miss something?
我是否错过某事?
No,she's still upset because I saw her boobies.
她很生气因为我看见她的胸脯
What were you doing seeing her boobies?
你看她的胸脯干吗?
It was an accident. I wasn't across the street with a telescope.
那是意外,我可不是隔条街用望远镜偷看
Can we change the subject,please?
能换个话题吗?
These aren't her "boobies." These are her breasts.
没错,因为那不是她的胸脯 而是她的胸部
Pheebs,I was hoping for more of a change.
菲比,我要的不只是改变字眼
I always liked "Bazoombas."
我向来喜欢“波涛汹涌”(俚语)
Gives them a Latin spin.
给他个拉丁旋转
Can we drop this already,please?
我们放下这个不说了,好不好?
Why are you embarrassed? They were very nice boobies.
你为什么要难为情呢? 它们确实是非常好看的胸脯
"Nice"? They were "nice"?
“好看”?他们很“好看”?
That's it? I mean,mittens are "nice."
就这样?手套也很好看
Okay. Rock,hard place. Me.
我…左右为难
You're so funny!
你真逗
He's really funny.
他真的很逗
I wouldn't wanna be there when the laughter stops.
他不笑的时候,我也不想待在这儿
Whoa,back up there,sparky.
等等,回去上句
What did you mean by that?
那是什么意思?
It seems that maybe you have intimacy issues...
你似乎有亲密上的问题
...that you use your humor to keep people at a distance.
你用你的幽默和人保持距离
I mean,I just met you. I don't know you from Adam.
我才刚认识你,我从亚当那里没听说过你
Only child,right?
独子?
Parents divorced before you hit puberty.
母在你青春期前离婚?
-How did you know that? -It's textbook.
-你怎会知道? -你很典型
Hey,you guys. You all know my dad,right?
各位,乔伊.你们都认识我爸吧?
-How long are you in the city? -Two days. I got a job.
-打算在纽约待多久? -就几天.我在市中心有工作
I'm better off staying with Joey...
我想和乔伊同住
...than going back and forth on the ferry.
比来回坐渡轮好
-I don't know this one. -This is my friend Roger.
-我没见过他 -他是我朋友罗杰
-Good to meet you. -You too.
-幸会,罗杰 -彼此彼此
-What happened to the puppet guy? -Dad.
-玩布偶的那个怎么了? -爸
Oh,excuse me. So,Ross,how's the wife?
抱歉,罗斯,你的太太呢?
0 for 2,huh?
两人出局了?
Chandler,say something funny.
钱德,说点好笑的
I gotta go. Miss you too.
我得挂电话了,我也想你
-I love you,but it's getting late -Say hi. Hey,Ma.
-我爱你,但现在很晚了 -让我向她打声招呼
I made the appointment with Dr. Bassida and
我和包西达大夫约了时间
Excuse me?
什么?
Did you know this isn't Ma?
你知道这不是妈吗?
Her name's Ronni.
她叫罗妮
She's a pet mortician.
宠物殡葬业者
Sure.
当然
So,how long you been...?
你和她多久了…
Remember when you were a kid, I'd take you to the navy yard?
记得小时候我常带你去海军军港看大船?
-Since then? -No,it's only been six years.
-从那时候就开始了? -不,才6年
I wanted you to think of a nice memory so you'd know I'm not a terrible guy.
我只想勾起你美好的回忆 让你不会觉得我一直是个大烂人
-What are you doing? -Chopping garlic.
-你们在干嘛? -切大蒜
You don't crush it?
你不是把他们压碎的吗?
You're having an affair, I chop garlic. It's a wacky world.
这是你的风格,我一向都是切的 真是个古怪的世界
Joe,you ever been in love?
乔伊,你爱过吗?
-I don't know. -Then you haven't.
-我不知道 -那就是没有
-You're burning tomatoes. -You're one to talk.
-你的蕃茄烧焦了 -别想转移话题
Your dad's in love. The worst part is, it's with two different women.
乔,你老爸爱得无法自拔 最糟的是我爱两个女人
Oh,man! Please tell me one of them is Ma.
拜托你告诉我其中一个是妈
Of course one of them's Ma. What's the matter with you?
当然其中一个是你妈,你是怎么搞的?
It's like if you woke up and found out...
这就像你某天起床突然发现
...your dad leads this double life.
你爸是个双面人
He's like actually some spy working for the ClA.
就像是为中情局工作的间谍
That'd be cool.
那一定很酷
This blows!
但这个很烂
Do you think Dad cheated?
你以为爸爸骗你吗?
I don't think so. That would involve sex.
我没有这么想 过.那一定包括了性是不是
I'd like to think that our parents don't do that.
我更加趋向于认为我父母没有那么做
I know. Why can't parents just stay parents?
为何父母就不能是父母?
Why do they have to become people? Why do they have?
为何他们就得成为人间男女? 为何他们要?
Why...
为什么…
...can't you stop staring at my breasts?
…别再盯着我的胸部看
What?
什么?
Didn't you get a good enough look?
那一天你还看得不够吗?
We're all adults here. There's only one way to resolve this.
我们都已是成年人 此事只有一个解决之道
Since you saw her boobies you have to show her your pee-pee.
既然你看过她的胸脯 你应该让她看你的小弟弟
You know, I don't see that happening.
办不到
Come on. He's right. Tit for tat.
拜托,他说得对.以眼还眼
Well,I'm not showing you my tat!
我不会让你看的
-It's Phoebe. -And Rog!
-是菲比 -还有罗杰!
Come on up.
快上来
Oh,good! Rog is here.
这下可好,罗杰来了
-What's the matter with Rog? -It's a little thing. I hate that guy!
-罗杰有什么不对劲吗? -没什么,小事.我讨厌这家伙
So he was a little analytical. That's what he does.
为什么?因为他太善于分析 他就是这种人别这样嘛
Come on,he's not that bad.
他没那么糟
You're wrong! Why would I marry her...
你错了!如果当初我感觉到
...if I thought that she was a lesbian?
感觉到她是女同志我何必和她结婚呢?
I don't know. Maybe you wanted your marriage to fail.
我不知道,或许你想让婚姻失败
Why? Why would l? Why?
为什么?我为什么这样?为什么?
I don't know. Maybe low self-esteem?
我不知道,或许自信心不足
Maybe to compensate for overshadowing a sibling. Maybe
或许是弥补你让你妹相形见绌的愧疚
Wait! Go back to that "sibling" thing.
或许…等等,回到妹妹的话题
Well,I don't know.
什么?我不知道
You could've sabotaged your marriage...
你要使你的婚姻触礁
...so the sibling would feel like less of a failure.
让你妹在父母面前不那么抬不起头
That's ridiculous! I don't feel guilty for her failures.
这太荒谬了 她不争气我并未感到自责
-You think I'm a failure? -lsn't he good?
-你认为我不争气? -他不错吧
Yeah. No,that's not what I was saying.
我不是那个意思?
I thought you were on my side.
多年来我以为你支持我
But maybe you sucked up to them so they'd favor you.
但或许你婚姻失败目的是想巴结爸妈 让他们更心疼你
I married a lesbian to make you look good!
我娶女同志是想让你建立自信
You're right. I mean,you're right.
你说得对.我说,你说得对
It wasn't just the Weebles, but the Weeble Play Palace...
那不是“威伯”的问题 而是威伯游乐宫
...and the Weeble's Cruise Ship...
和威伯游轮的问题
...with this lifeboat for the Weebles to wobble in.
它上面的救生艇让威伯能缓缓驶出
And Mom just gave them all away.
偏偏妈妈把他们都给出去了
That's tough,tough stuff.
那滋味不好受
Pheebs,we're gonna catch that movie, we gotta go.
菲比,如果想看电影我们现在该走了
-Feel better. -We're gonna be late,sweetie.
-打起精神来,瑞秋 -菲比,我们快来不及了
-Thanks for everything,Mon. -No problem.
-谢谢你做的一切,摩妮卡 -不客气
Listen,it was great seeing you again.
各位,很高兴和各位再度见面
Mon,easy on those cookies,okay?
摩妮卡,饼乾别吃太多
Remember,they're just food, they're not love.
切记,那只是食物,不是爱
I hate that guy!
我讨厌这家伙
Good night,you guys.
晚安,各位
Oh,look. It's the woman we ordered.
这是我们订的女人
Hey,can we help you?
需要帮忙吗?
No,thanks. I'm just waiting for Joey Tribbiani.
不用,谢谢,我在等乔依
I'm Joey Tribbiani.
我就是乔依
Oh,no,not you. Big Joey. Oh,my God!
不是你,是老乔依,天啊
You're so much cuter than your pictures.
你此照片上帅多了
I'm Ronni.
我是罗妮
Cheese Nip?
想吃起司块(夹子)吗?
Joey's having an embolism, but I'd go for a nip.
乔伊有“栓子”,我要个“夹子”
Most people, when their pets pass on...
大部份人在宠物过世后
...want them like they're sleeping.
希望它们就像长眠一样
Occasionally you get a person who wants them in a pose.
但有些人要他们摆出姿势
Like chasing their tail.
像追自己的尾巴
Or jumping to catch a Frisbee.
跳起接住飞盘
Joey,if I go first, I wanna be looking for my keys.
乔伊,如果我先走 我的姿势要像找钥匙一样
-That's a good one! -Hey.
-这姿势不错! -嗨!
Hey,Dad. Ronni's here.
嗨,爸爸.罗妮来了
-Hi. -Hey.
-嗨 -嘿
Hello,babe! What are you doing here?
宝贝,你来干什么?
Oh,you left your hair at my place.
你的假发留在我的住处
I thought you'd need it tomorrow.
我想你明天用得上
Thank you.
谢谢
So,who's up for a big game of Kerplunk?
谁想玩“科普朗克”?
Look,I shouldn't have come.
我不该来这儿
I better go. I'll miss the train.
我该走了,我不想错过最后一班地铁
-I don't want you taking that thing. -Where do I stay? Here?
-不,我不要你坐这么晚的车 -我要住哪儿?这里?
We'll go to a hotel.
我们去住饭店
-No,you won't. -No,we won't.
-不行 -不行
If you go to a hotel, you'll be doing stuff.
你们去饭店就一定会办事
I want you here so I can keep an eye on you.
我要你们待在这儿,这样我就可以监视
-You're gonna keep an eye on us? -Right.
-你要监视我们 -没错
As long as you are under my roof...
只要住在我家
...you're gonna live by my rules.
―切就得听我的
That means no sleeping with your girlfriend.
那就是不准你们睡在一起
Wow,he's strict.
他好严格
Dad,you'll be in my room. You can stay in Chandler's room.
爸,你睡我房间 罗妮,你睡钱德的房间
And Chandler will be?
那钱德呢?
Out here with me,bunking up.
在这和我一起,轮船铺位
Oh,bunking up. If you smell s'mores, don't be alarmed.
轮船铺位.如果问到烟味 不要拉警报哦
Thanks. You're a good kid.
谢谢,你真是个好孩子
I'll show you to my room.
我带你去看我房间
That sounds weird not followed by, "No,it's late."
感觉真奇怪 你没说“不,谢了,时候不早了”
This is just for tonight. Tomorrow you gotta change.
只有今晚,明天你们就得做出改变
Change?
改变?
-Break up with Ronni -I can't!
-和罗妮分手 -我不能!
Then come clean with Ma! This is not right!
不然就是向妈自首,这样是不对的
I don't wanna hear it! Now go to my room!
对,但是…我不想听,快进我房里
Hey,kickie!
别踢了
-What are you doing? -Getting comfortable.
-你在干什么? -找寻舒适的位置
-I can't sleep in my underwear. -Well,you're gonna.
-穿着内裤我睡不着 -你非穿不可
I was thinking about how I'm always seeing girls on top of girls....
我一直在想… 我总是看见女人叠在女人上面
Are they end-to-end, or tall,like pancakes?
她们是首尾相接,还是是像煎饼一样叠起来
You know,how I date all these women.
懂我意思吗? 我总想像自己和所有这些女人约会
I always figured,when the right one comes along...
因为我总想梦中情人出现时
... I'll be able to go the distance.
我就会勇往直前,坚持到最后
Now I'm looking at my dad,thinking
但如今看见我爸…看起来
You're not him,you're you.
你不是他,你是你自己
When they wanted you in your father's business,did you cave?
当全天下都希望你继承你爸的事业时 你有屈服吗?
-No. -No.
-No.-No.-没有.-没有
You chose the out-of-work-actor business.
你决心从事没有工作的演员事业
That wasn't easy,but you did it.
这不是一件容易的事,但你办到了
I believe when the right woman comes along...
我也相信梦中情人出现时
...you'll have the guts to say, "No,thanks,I'm married."
你会有勇气对她说“抱歉,我已婚”
-You really think so? -Yeah,I really do.
-你真的这样认为? -真的
-Thanks,Chandler. -Get off!
-谢谢,钱德 -滚开
-Hi. -Hi. May I help you?
-Hi -有事吗?
Joey said I could use your shower since Chandler's in ours.
乔伊说我能用你的浴室 因为钱德正在用我们的
Okay. Who are you?
ok.你是谁?
Oh,I'm Ronni. Ronni Rapalono.
我叫罗妮. 罗妮.拉帕罗罗
The mistress?
情妇
-Come on in. -Thanks.
-请进 -谢谢
I'm Rachel. Bathroom's there.
我叫瑞秋.浴室在那儿
Ronni,how long has Chandler been in the shower?
罗妮,钱德进浴室多久了?
Oh,like five minutes.
约5分钟
Perfect.
太好了
Fasten your seat belts, it's pee-pee time.
请系好安全带,“小弟弟”时间到了
-Hey,Mr. Trib. -Hey,good morning,dear.
-崔先生 -早安
Chandler Bing, it's time to see your thing.
钱德,该我看你的小弟弟了
-What's with you? -I thought it was Chandler!
-你是怎么搞的?  -我以为你是钱德
You were supposed to be in there so I'd see your thing!
你应该在浴室 这样我才能看见你的小弟弟
Sorry,my thing was in there with me.
抱歉,我的小弟弟和我在那儿
-How's it going? -Good.
-如何? -不错
Roger's having a dinner thing. He wanted me to invite you guys.
罗杰想邀大家一起吃晚餐
-So,what's going on? -Nothing.
-怎么了? -没事
It's just....
只是…
It's Roger,you know?
罗杰,我说不上来
There's something about
有些事…
We just feel that he's....
基本上我们认为他…
-We hate that guy! -We hate him!
-我们讨厌他… -我们讨厌他…
-We're sorry,Pheebs. -Okay.
-菲此,我们很抱歉 -ok
Don't you think it's just that he's so perceptive...
是不是他观察入微
...it freaked you out?
反而吓到你们了
No,we hate him!
不,我们讨厌他…
I'm sorry.
抱歉
-Ma! What are you doing here? -I came to give you this and this!
-妈,你来干什么? -我拿这个来给你,还有这个
Big ring!
大戒指!
Why'd you fill your father's head with garbage...
你为什么要对你爸讲一大堆
...about making things right?
关于改正的垃圾呢?
Things were fine this way!
何不顺其自然呢?
There's chicken in there. Put it away.
里面有鸡肉,拿去放好
For God's sake,Joey! Really.
拜托,乔依,真的
-Hold on. You knew? -Of course I knew. What do you think?
-慢着,你都知道? -我当然知道,你认为呢?
Your father is no James Bond.
你爸又不是詹姆士庞德
You should've heard his stories.
你应该听过他的谎言
"I'm sleeping over at my accountant's."
“我在会计这儿睡”
-What is that? Please! -So then,how could you?
-那是什么?拜托 -你怎能…
Do you remember how your father used to be?
记得你爸以前的模样吗?
Always yelling. Nothing made him happy.
总是大吼大叫,总是不开心
Not that wood shop,not those stupid little ships in the bottle.
连木店和瓶内的小船也无法让他开心
Now he's happy. I mean,it's nice. He has a hobby.
这样也好,他总算有个嗜好
Ma,I don't mean to be disrespectful...
妈,恕我直言
... but what the hell are you talking about?
你到底在说什么?
-I mean,what about you? -Me? I'm fine.
-我是说,你怎么样? -我很好啊
Look,honey,in an ideal world...
在理想的世界中没有她
...there'd be no her and your father would look like Sting.
没有她,你爸也长得和史汀一样帅
And something else:
再告诉你别的
Ever since that poodle-stuffer came along...
自从那女人出现后
... he's so ashamed of himself that he's been more attentive.
他感到内疚而开始对我体贴
He's been more loving. It's like every day is our anniversary.
每天都像我们的结婚纪念日
-I'm happy for you? -Well,don't be!
-我该为你高兴? -不需要
Now everything's screwed up.
因为现在全搞砸了
I just want it the way it was.
我只想回到从前
Ma,I'm sorry.
妈,对不起
I just did what I thought you'd want.
我自以为做了你想做的事
I know you did,cookie. I know you did.
我知道,亲爱的,我知道
So tell me. Did you see her?
告诉我,你看见她没?
Yeah.
看到了
-You're 10 times prettier than she is. -That's sweet.
-你比她漂亮十倍都不止 -嘴巴真甜
Could I take her?
我斗得过她?
With this ring,no contest.
你有戒指,她斗不过的
Oh,no! Don't ever do that!
oh,不!永远不要这样做!
-What? -I'm sorry.
-什么? -对不起
I have a thing, which means you can't ever do that!
我有一样东西, 意味着你永远不要这么做
-What's wrong,sweetie? -Nothing.
-怎么了? -没事
-No,what's wrong? Come on. -Okay.
-到底怎么了?快说嘛 -ok
It's nothing. I'm fine. It's just It's my friends.
好吧,我…没事 问题出在我朋友身上
They have a liking problem with you...
他们对你有意见
...in that they don't.
他们…
They don't?
They don't? 他们?
But they don't see all the wonderfulness that I see.
他们看不见你的好处
They don't see all the good and sweet stuff.
他们看不见你好的一面
-They think you're a little -What?
-他们认为你有点… -什么?
Intense and creepy.
难以相处
-Oh. -But I don't. Me,Phoebe.
-oh -但我菲比不这么认为
-I'm not at all surprised about that. -That's why you're so great.
-我对他们的反应毫不感到惊讶. -这就是我欣赏你的地方
It's quite typical behavior...
当群体动力失调时
...when you have this kind of dysfunctional group dynamic.
这是很平常的反应
You know,this kind of codependent, emotionally stunted...
这种相互依赖,情绪激动
...sitting in your stupid coffeehouse, with your stupid big cups...
坐在那家烂咖啡屋, 拿着又大又蠢的咖啡杯
...which might as well have nipples on them.
或许还有乳头在上面
And you're all like, "Oh,define me! Define me!
你们都会说“定义我这个人”
Love me! I need love!
爱我,我需要爱
You talked to your dad?
你和你爸谈过了?
He's gonna keep cheating on Ma like she wanted.
他要以我妈希望的方式继续欺骗我妈
Ma will keep pretending she doesn't know.
我妈要继续假装她一无所知
And my sister,Tina, can't see her husband.
我妹蒂娜不能再见她丈夫
He got a restraining order.
因为他接到禁制令
Which has nothing to do with it. I found out today.
这两件事没关系,但我今天才听说
Things have changed here on Waltons'mountain.
沃顿山这儿的事全变了
-So,Joey,are you okay? -Yeah,I guess.
-乔伊,你没事吧? -或许吧
It's just You know,they're parents.
他们是…父母
After a certain point, you gotta let go.
你不得不顺其自然,即使你知道这样做不对
You gotta let them make their own mistakes.
但你还是得让他们犯自己的错误
And think,in a few years, we'll turn into them.
而且几年后我们就和他们一样
Oh,please.
拜托
If I turn into my parents,I'll be an alcoholic blond chasing men...
如果我像他们一样 我不是变成追逐金发帅哥的酒鬼
...or I'll end up like my mom!
就是变得和我妈一样
-Hey. -Hey,Pheebs.
-嗨 -嗨.菲比
How's it going?
怎么样?
Okay,except I broke up with Roger.
还好,只是我和罗杰分手了
-Yeah,right. -No,no,really.
-没错 -不…真的
-What happened? -I don't know. I mean...
-怎么了? -我说不上来
... he's a good person, and he can be really sweet.
他是个好人而且对我很体贴
In some ways, I think he is so right for me.
他的某些方面很适合我
It's just.... I hate that guy!
只是…我讨厌这个人
Hi,Joey. What's going on?
Hi,乔伊.怎么样?
Clear the tracks for the boobie payback.
为胸脯债务清理跑道
Next stop,Rachel Greene.
下一站,瑞秋.格林
Joey,what the hell were you doing?
乔伊,你在干什么?
Sorry,wrong boobies!
对不起,错误的胸脯!
Hello,Joey!
乔伊!
Hello,dear!
亲爱的!